besocial.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy - BeSocial

### 

BeSocial.com

Privacy Policy

Created: July 23, 2015

Last Updated: July 23, 2015

Protranstech BV DBA Netherlands Besloten vennootschap respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website, BeSocial.com ("Website") and our practices for collecting, using, keeping, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website (including desktop and mobile versions).
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * When you interact with this Website through third-party social media platforms.
  * It does not apply to information collected by:
  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Belgrano or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from (or on) the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regardingyour information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change on one or more occasions. We will consider your continued use of the Website after we make changes asyour acceptance of the changes, so please check the policy frequently for updates. 

#### 1\. Are minors welcome on BeSocial?

You can only become a registered user of BeSocial if you are 18-years old and have reached the age of majority in the county where you live if that age happens to be greater than 18. That means that we do not knowingly collect any information about children, minors, or anyone under the age of majority. Nor do we knowingly market to children, minors, or anyone under 18-years old. If you are under 18-years old, we request that you do not submit information to us. If we become aware that a child, minor, or anyone under 18-years old has registered with us and provided us with personal information, we will take steps to cancel that person's registration and delete their profile information from BeSocial. If we do delete a profile because you breached our no children rules, we may keep your email and IP address to make sure that you do not try to get around our rules by creating a new profile.

Under 47 U.S.C. § 230(d), we notify you that parental control protections (including computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. You may find information about providers of these protections on the Internet by searching "parental control protection" or similar terms. If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using any of the following products provided for informational purposes only and not endorsed by us: [CYBERsitter™](http://www.cybersitter.com/) | [Net Nanny®](http://www.netnanny.com/) | [CyberPatrol](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/) | [ASACP](http://www.asacp.org/).

#### 2\. What types of information do we collect about you and how do we collect it?

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website or service, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, including your name, email address, date of birth, or any other information that the Website collects that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under law ("personal information");
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, including your age, gender, location, and any other optional information you provide about yourself in your profile; or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

Information You Provide to Us

  * The information we collect on or through our Website may include:
  * Information that you provide by filing in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, completing your profile, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website or service. 
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your requests. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website or to receive payments from us.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed ("posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "user contributions"). Your user contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although you may set certain privacy settings for this information by logging into your account, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your user contributions. Thus, we cannot and do not guarantee that your user contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. 

Information We Collect through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may keep it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by allowing us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies).A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. But if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. If you want to learn more about cookies, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). To learn more about how we use cookies, please see our cookie statement.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies, but you can access your Flash management tools from [Adobe's website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).
  * Web Beacons.Pages of our Website (and our emails) may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages (or opened an email) and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). If you want to learn more about web beacons, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/)

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us. 

Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control third-party tracking technologies or how third parties' use them. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. 

Social Networks and Third-Party Plug-ins

Our Website includes plugins from social networks and other third parties. An example of a plugin is the Facebook "Like" button. Where legally permitted, these plugins may communicate with and send information to the party that provided the plugin, even if you do not click on the plugin. This information may include your IP address, information about your browser and device, and the address of the webpage you are visiting on our Website. Loading, using, or clicking the plugins may also place, read, and transmit cookies. These cookies may contain a unique identifier the social network or third party assigns you. The loading, functionality, and your use of the plugins are governed by the privacy policy and terms of the party that provided the plugin. 

Social Network and Third-Party Login

Our Website allows you to log in using a social network or other third-party account. An example of a third-party login is "Log in with Facebook." Logging into our Website with your social network or other third-party account may allow us to gather information that you give us permission to access from that social network or third party. The login feature may also transfer information to the social network or third party, including your username and password, to authenticate you. The social network or third party may also automatically collect information like your IP address, information about your browser and device, and the address of the webpage you are visiting on our Website. The login feature may also place and read cookies from that third party that may contain a unique identifier the social network or other third party assigns to you. The functionality of and your use of the login is governed by the privacy policy and terms of the party that provided the login functionality.

#### 3\. How do we use your information?

  * We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information. 

We may use the information we have collected from you to allow us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria. 

If you have registered with one or more of our partner websites, including Facebook, or you have verified your account through a partner website, we may connect your BeSocial profile with your profile on that partner website. We may do this by way of new products and applications that we introduce on one or more occasions, including new products powered by Belgrano. 

#### 4\. With whom do we share your information?

  * We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.
  * We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:
  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Belgrano's assets, whether as a going concerning or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Belgrano about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.
  * We may also disclose your personal information:
  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms and other agreements, including for payment or for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Belgrano, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### 5\. When you put information about yourself on BeSocial, what do the other users see?

To make sure you get to meet as many people as possible on BeSocial, other users get to see your user name and any information you post on your profile, including photos if you select the "photo privacy" setting on the account settings page. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want other BeSocial users to know about you. You can also choose to limit the information that other users see by adjusting your "privacy settings" on the account settings page. 

We recommend and encourage you (and all our users) to think carefully about the information you disclose about yourself, and suggest that you follow our Safety Tips. We also do not recommend that you put email addresses, URLs, instant messaging details, phone numbers, full name or address, credit card details, national identity numbers, drivers' license details, or other sensitive information in your profile, which is open to abuse and misuse. 

Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself on your profile, including your religious denomination and health details. While you may voluntarily provide this information to us when you create your profile, including your sexual preferences and ethnic background, there is no requirement to do so. Please remember that photographs or any video clips that you post on BeSocial may reveal these kinds of sensitive personal data. Where you do upload and choose to tell us sensitive information about yourself, you are expressly consenting to our processing your information and making this public to other users.

When you post information about yourself or use the messaging system, the amount of personal information you share is at your own risk. If you post anything that is inconsistent with our terms, we may terminate your account.

#### 6\. What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information?

We strive to provide you with choices about the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on [Adobe's website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). To learn how you can manage your other cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly. 
  * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link on any received email messages or at any time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your Account Settings by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@BeSocial.com.
  * Promotional Offers from the Company.If you do not want to have your email address used by Belgrano to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by usingt he provided unsubscribe links in received emails or at any other time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@BeSocial.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions or click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email. This opt out does not apply to information provided to Belgrano because of a service purchase or other transactions.
  * Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt-out via the provided unsubscribe links in received email messages. You can also always adjust your user advertising preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@BeSocial.com. For this opt-out to function, you must have your browser set to accept browser cookies. 

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. But these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the [NAI's website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Warning: If you have created a BeSocial profile through Facebook and you do not want to link your BeSocial profile to your Facebook profile, BeSocial cannot amend these settings. Please visit the application settings on Facebook and follow the instructions to remove the BeSocial access permissions.

#### 7\. How do you access and correct your information?

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at privacy@BeSocial.com to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your user contributions from the Website, copies of your user contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Our terms govern proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including user contributions.

#### 8\. Can you hide or deleteyour profile?

If you have registered on BeSocial, you can cancel or hide your account at any time by going to the My Settings control on BeSocial when you are logged in and choosing the "hide account" or "cancel account" link. Hiding your profile means that no user can search for you on the Website although they might still see your profile from direct cached links, but it will not be deleted. We save your profile information in case you later decide to restore your account. We save your profile information in case you later decide to restore your account. Many users cancel their accounts for temporary reasons and in doing so expect us to keep their information until they return to BeSocial (if this is not true for you, please contact us and we will delete your information). You will thus be able to restore your account and your profile in its entirety within six months of canceling it. 

After the expiration of six months, we permanently delete your account from BeSocial. We delete photographs from our servers no later than 14 days after the expiration of the six month period while we delete other information (like contact history) over a longer timescale, by way of periodic housekeeping. You should only delete your account if you are certain you never want to restore it. 

To prevent abuse or misuse of BeSocial by a user, after termination or deletion of a profile/account, we will keep the information we consider necessary to make sure that user does not open a new account and profile in breach of our terms and to ensure compliance with all laws. 

Warning: Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may still be viewable or accessed on the Internet if you have previously shared that information with others, or copied or stored by other users or if that information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control this, nor will we be liable for this. If you have given third-party applications or websites access to your personal information, they may retain that information if permitted under their terms or privacy policies.

Removed or delete information may persist in backup copies for up to 30 days to allow restoration, but will not be available to others in the meantime. 

#### 9\. How do we protect your personal information?

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, change, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like your profile. Any user of the Website may view the information you share in public areas. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

#### 10\. Where is your personal information kept?

This privacy policy is intended to cover collection of information on or through our Website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to make sure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy. When you provide personal information to us through the services, you consent to the processing of your data in, and the transfer of your data to, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers host these services.

#### 11\. Third-Party Websites

There may be a number of places on our Website or through our services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this privacy policy.For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our Website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. Once you leave our digital environment, we are no longer responsible for and cannot control what is collected on these websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.

#### 12\. DMCA Takedown Requests

This Website complies with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. If you reasonably believe your copyrighted work has been used or posted by a third party without your consent, you may follow the instructions on our DMCA Page on how to report it. 

By submitting a copyright infringement notice or other communication (including communications about content stored on or transmitted through the Website), you consent to have these communications forwarded to the person or entity who stored, transmitted, or linked to the content addressed by your communication, in order to facilitate a prompt resolution. We forward DMCA infringement notices (including any personally identifying information contained in the notices) as submitted to us without any deletions.

#### 13\. Do Not Track

Do Not Track ("DNT") is a privacy preference that you can set in your browser. DNT is a way for you to inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information we collect and that is why we provide you the ability to opt-out. But we do not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. For more information about DNT signals, you may visit www.allaboutdnt.com.

#### 14\. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make this request, please send an email to privacy@BeSocial.com.

#### 15\. Canada Privacy Rights

BeSocial complies with Canadian Federal and Provincial privacy laws and regulations including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.BeSocial will only use your personal information for the purposes intended and as detailed in this privacy policy unless we have obtained your consent to use it for other purposes.

Residents of Canada are notified that the personal information they provide to BeSocial is stored in BeSocial's databases outside of Canada including in the United States and may be subject to disclosure to authorized law enforcement or government agencies in response to lawful demand under the laws of that country. 

If you need to contact BeSocial about your personal information, please email us at privacy@BeSocial.com. 

#### 16\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat your personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The privacy policy identifies when we last updated it at the top of the page.You are responsible for making sure we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for frequently visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

#### 17\. Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at privacy@BeSocial.com.
